myvideotalk.com 2018-01-07

# PRIVACY STATEMENT

PRIVACY STATEMENT
At MyVideoTalk, we take the information you share with us very seriously. MyVideoTalk is the sole
owner of the information collected on our Sites. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to
others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Policy (including as it may be amended—see
below).
Your Acceptance of These Terms
Your continued use of MyVideoTalk products, services and websites signifies your consent to the
MyVideoTalk Privacy Policy. This policy is reviewed periodically by MyVideoTalk management and
may be subject to change.
Information Gathered and Tracked
We collect information about you when you visit and use the Site, and particularly when you enter
or input information, whether during the course of entering, initiating, fulfilling and transmitting
information or otherwise in connection with your general activities and/or use of the Site. You may
however, use this site without disclosing any personal information about yourself.
If you are submitting personally identifiable information on behalf of others in your business for
registration purposes or otherwise, you represent that you have their permission, agreement and
full authorization to provide this information to us for these purposes. If we determine that such
authorization has not been properly obtained, we may immediately and without notice, discontinue
your authorized use of those features of the Site for which you have registered.
MyVideoTalk uses cookies. This improves the convenience and efficiency of your experience when
using our products and services. A cookie is data stored on the user's hard drive which links to
statistical information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally
identifiable information
How Does MyVideoTalk Use My Information
In the purchase process you are required to provide contact information (such as name, shipping
address, phone number, and email address) . We use this information to communicate with you
about your account, to notify you about important functionality changes to the web site, new
services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable, company emails and newsletters. If we have
trouble processing an order, we use this contact information to get in touch with you. Demographic
information provided at time of purchase process may also be given to the selling representative to
assure quality customer care.
We may disclose aggregated information about our members but that information contains no
personal information. In some situations, we share personal information with third parties who
provide support for the internal operations or enhancement of the services. Due to the existing
regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other
personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal
information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may
unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you can
authorize us to) disclose any personal information about you to law enforcement or other
government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection
with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or
may expose us to legal liability.
Security
We make every effort to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of our users information under our
control. In addition, we, and our partners, always use a secure connection when collecting personal
financial information from you. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed
to be 100% secure.
If MyVideoTalk receives any type of financial lien (including IRS tax lien, court lien, etc.) on your
account, your account will be cancelled until proven that the lien has been paid off. Upon receiving
such lien a copy is immediately sent to the tax payer and all directions given by the court, IRS, etc.
will be followed promptly. We must receive a Termination of Order to Withhold form in order to
bring your account back to good standing.
Questions or Concerns About Our Privacy
If you have any questions concerning our Privacy Policy, or if you do not understand any of the terms
or disclosures noted above, you may contact us at: Support@MyVideoTalk.com
